{
  "quizes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is 3 x 4?",
          "answers": ["34", "12", "7", "1"],
          "correctAnswer": "12"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is 5 x 0?",
          "answers": ["0", "12", "7", "1"],
          "correctAnswer": "0"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is 8 x 3?",
          "answers": ["34", "12", "24", "1"],
          "correctAnswer": "24"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is 10 x 100?",
          "answers": ["34", "1000", "7", "1"],
          "correctAnswer": "1000"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is 6 x 7?",
          "answers": ["34", "12", "7", "42"],
          "correctAnswer": "42"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Geography",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "How many GreatLakes does Michigan have?",
          "answers": ["5", "12", "7", "1"],
          "correctAnswer": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "What continent does Argentina belong to?",
          "answers": ["South America", "North America", "Europe", "Asia"],
          "correctAnswer": "South America"
        },
        {
          "question": "What ocean is the largest?",
          "answers": ["Atlantic", "Indian", "Arctic", "Pacific"],
          "correctAnswer": "Pacific"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the most previous Super Continent?",
          "answers": ["Big Land", "Ontana", "Pangea", "Earth"],
          "correctAnswer": "Pangea"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the country Egypt?",
          "answers": ["Egypt", "Not Egypt", "It has no name", "What is Egypt?"],
          "correctAnswer": "Egypt"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 630069968,
      "name": "React",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What are the building blocks of React?",
          "answers": ["Elements", "Components", "Trees", "Blocks"],
          "correctAnswer": "Components"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who invented React?",
          "answers": ["Google", "Chrome", "Ian", "Facebook"],
          "correctAnswer": "Facebook"
        },
        {
          "question": "What are functions that begin with 'use' called?",
          "answers": ["Hooks", "Functions", "React", "Spears"],
          "correctAnswer": "Hooks"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the most common React hook?",
          "answers": ["useEffect", "useReducer", "useState", "useCallback"],
          "correctAnswer": "useState"
        },
        {
          "question": "State can be passed down to a child component via...",
          "answers": ["Props", "Love", "Magic", "React"],
          "correctAnswer": "Props"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 906390703,
      "name": "Aba",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is Aba's name?",
          "answers": ["Ava", "Aba", "Not Aba", "Abababa"],
          "correctAnswer": "Aba"
        },
        {
          "question": "How tall is Aba?",
          "answers": ["5ft", "2ft", "short", "10ft"],
          "correctAnswer": "short"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is Aba's favorite drink?",
          "answers": ["Kool-aid", "Beer", "Coke", "Dr. Pepper"],
          "correctAnswer": "Dr. Pepper"
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does Aba live?",
          "answers": ["The moon", "Kansas", "I don't Know", "Royal Oak"],
          "correctAnswer": "Royal Oak"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which one would Aba choose?",
          "answers": ["Taco Bell", "McDonalds", "Burger King", "KFC"],
          "correctAnswer": "McDonalds"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who does Aba Love most?",
          "answers": ["God", "Grimace", "Ian", "Smiski"],
          "correctAnswer": "Grimace"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 137684567,
      "name": "TEST",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "This is a test question",
          "answers": ["test", "still testing", "yes still a test", "cmon now"],
          "correctAnswer": "test"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
